Good day to all of you watching
this video. I am Deng Bautista your trusted Sun
Life advisor. Today I will present to
you the most affordable sunlight
policy that you can consider
getting if you are on a tight
budget. This is the Sun Life assure life
insurance.
What is Sun Life assure? This
is an insurance for Health.
It covers 36 critical illnesses. It also has
life insurance protection.
It is also automatically renewable. So let's see
what this is about.
This is a non-participating
5-year renewable term. So when
we say non-participating, it is not
like other insurance that
we get an endowment or additional
funds that are withdrawn because
it is really focused on life
insurance. So it is a 5-year renewable
term. So you can renew it after
5 years. But we are covered until 70
years old. Its coverage is that
we can add an Accidental death
benefit and it also includes the
total disability
benefit. So let me give you a sample
of the policy. This is Sun Life sure.
I advise our clients who are
a little bit older, in their early
40s, who are thinking about having life
insurance, but their budget is tight,
so let's try to calculate a
40-year-old female who is non-smoker, so
Sun Life assures us.
We can have a face
amount of 500,000, so when we say face
amount, this is the amount that
our beneficiaries get in case we
have an untimely death.
We are a little bit ahead, so that's what we can get and
pass on to our
beneficiaries. So we can also
add an Accidental Deb benefit,
which is 500,000, in case we are
the cause of the accident.
We can get 500,000 plus the face
amount of 500, 100,000. So
our beneficiary will get 1 million as the
total disability benefit. That's the
k-center. She's
alive, but she's
totally disabled. She no longer has
the ability to pay, so the good news is that
there's sunlight.  We will cover
our premium payment,
so for example,
we got it for about a year, 2
years or even less than a year, and then
we had that incident, so
don't worry because
it will be covered by
sunlight, so let's see what the
36 critical illnesses
it covers. So this is it. Once
we have any of the critical
illnesses, we will automatically have
500,000,
so the 500,000 face amount is
either by death or by critical illness,
so which ever comes first. For
example, if we have a
critical illness,
our
policy coverage is over, because that's all it is. It's
either critical illness or death, so
these are the critical illnesses that
Sun Life assure covers, first of all, heart
attack, very common, stroke, cancer, kidney
failure, what else are common
here, bacterial meningitis, encephalitis,
Parkinson's disease, and stage
liver failure, then next.  Those are the
critical illnesses that require surgery,
major organ transplant, coronary artery
bypass surgery or surgery for disease of
the Aorta replacement of the heart valve. That's it. So
to be eligible
for the critical illnesses, it's not like this is
immediate. For
example, we paid today,
suddenly it happened. First, it must have exceeded
90 days to activate
our use of our
insurance.
Okay, you will not pay the benefit if the
life insured is suffering from critical
illnesses diagnosed within 90 days from
the effective date of the
policy. Then the next step is this.
What is the mode of payment? So, for the
first 5 years, the
payment is a basic premium of 5,000
plus total disability
benefit. That's
6.6, so that's our annual
premium payment of
6,610. So it's really low. You can
pay it quarterly, so it will come out
at least
2,200. So calculate that if
you save every day, maybe around
7.  150 weekly so you can generate at least
700 for within 3 months, you will have
21 at least Php2,000. That's it. You have a
quarterly one so isn't
this sunlife really affordable, I
assure you. If ever you're
interested, my
Facebook page is in the description. You can send
a message if you just want to
ask, pretend to be cute about your age and
I will answer you right away or you
can also comment here on our YouTube
channel. Like Nain and subscribe so you can
see my next
videos. Thank you.